PHAM TRUNG TINH

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: Pham Trung Tinh

Date of birth: 10th September 1979 (39 years old)

Gender: Male

Nationality: Vietnamese

Married With 11 yrs. old son + 8 yrs. old daughter

Mobile: +81 70-2613-7556

Email: nasake.pham@gmail.com

Address: \mp 980-0011 Japan, Miyagi-ken, Sendai-shi, Aoba-ku, Kamisugi, 1-7-28



PROFILE & WORKING MIND SET

With nearly 15 years' experience in automotive industrial, especially, was educated well by Japanese top level companies/brands - Honda motor and Nissan motor limited.

Direct Working under top management of Japanese, Dennis, and Malaysian.

Working mind set: Doing effort to be the most believable in the company.

OUTSTANDING EXPERIENCES:

- 1. Have experienced to build up 2 big Japanese brands Honda and Nissan in Vietnam.
- 2. Have modern knowledge and professional working style.
- 3. Have ambition of building up new brand name
- 4. Can speak Japanese and understand Japanese culture

STRENGTHENS OF WORKING SKILLS:

- 1. Management skill: good in coaching, communication, organization, problem solving, scheduling, motivating...
- 2. Sales skill: Planning, training, negotiation, big fleet handling, building good relationship with customers, dealers, agents...
- 3. Marketing/branding: Proven abilities and skills in public communication, promotion, social events conducting, online/digital marketing...
- 4. Dealer development: good relationship with big investors nationwide, apply high showroom standard for both hardware (facility) and software (manpower) for outstanding competitiveness.
- 5. Others: Professional with a positive attitude, high level of enthusiasm and creative energy. Group working or independently, extremely responsible, resourceful and reliable with all tasks and assignments.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Company/brand	Experienced	Achievement/Remark
HONDA Honda Vietnam - Motorbike	From Sep'02 to May'05 (3 years) Job title: Assistant to Senior Manager (Japanese) Main Job: 1. Sales planning: responsible for short/mid - term target 2. Analysis market/competitors result and make proposal for countermeasures. 3. Manage nationwide HEAD sales operation: daily retail sales, stock and back order 4. Sales & marketing training to HEAD for HMMS course 5. Co-ordinate with marketing department for branding & CR activities: I love Vietnam campaign; Asimo show campaign, Honda fun fair 6. Budget management	Developed I love Vietnam campaign Handled Honda fun fair campaign
HONDA Honda Vietnam - Automobile	From May'05 to May'09 (4 years) Pham Trung Tinh Aning Staffior Managem Honda Vietnam Co., Ltd. Office: The (set) viet Touce: 1988 They Gov. 2009 Date., Heavel, Vietnam 1988 487349) Westilia: 1thig Touce: 1988 They Gov. 2009 Tay Lat., Heavel, Vietnam 1988 487349 Westilia: 1thig Towns Income. 1988 They Gov. 2009 Tay Lat., Heavel, Vietnam 1988 487349 Westilia: 1thig Towns Income. 1988 They Gov. 2009 Tay Lat., Heavel, Vietnam 1988 487349 Westilia: 1thig Towns Income. 1988 1898 1898 487349 Westilia: 1thig Towns Income. 1988 1898 1898 487349 Westilia: 1thig Towns Income. 1988 1898 1898 1898 1898 1898 1898 189	Honda Automobile Dealer Agreement Signing Ceremony Developed Honda automobile dealer network

- 8. Budget management for sales operation
- Co-ordinate with marketing department to implement branding, advertisement, sales promotion, social events, digital marketing, email marketing...
- Co-ordinate with After sales department to implement services campaigns
- 11. Co-ordinate with logistic department for vehicle delivery management
- 12. Other assignments and projects



Responsible for company and dealer sales achievement

From May'09 to current (8 years, 1 month)



NISSAN VIETNAM CO., LTD.
3"Floor, PVI Tower, No.1 Pham Van Bach Street,
Yen Hoa Ward, Cau Giay District, Hanoi
Phone: (+84) (4) 7301 1333 Fax: (+84) (4) 7302 2333
Mobile: (+84) 90 488 5009
Email: tinh.pham@nissan.com.vn
Websilte: www.rissan.com.vn
Tax code: 0103008177

Job title: Sales Manager

Main job:

- 1. Develop company business process
- Responsible for short & mid-term business plan
- 3. Responsible for production plan: model volume & color
- 4. Responsible for stock allocation to dealer
- 5. Follow dealer payment
- 6. Budget management
- Responsible for implementation of NSSW (Nissan Sales & Services Way) to internal & dealer network
- Responsible for implementation of S-DOM (Sales-Dealer Operation Mandatory)
- Dealer development: selecting dealer based on standardized conditions
- 10. Set up dealer sales organization and personal job description
- 11. Conduct sales training: Nissan brand training, customer handling process, product training, customer complaint handling and hospitality training courses



Developed Nissan dealer network



Launch Nissan products



Welcome Mr. Carlos Ghosn – Nissan CEO



Nissan Vietnam Limited

- 12. Co-ordinate with marketing department to implement branding, advertisement, sales promotion, social events, digital marketing, email marketing...
- 13. Co-ordinate with After sales department to implement services campaigns
- Coordinate with logistic (SCM)
 department for car delivery to dealer
 nationwide
- 15. Started Infiniti brand in Vietnam: studied luxury market, finding showroom, set up personnel...
- 16. Conducted CS survey and improve customer satisfaction
- 17. Responsible for fleet sales
- 18. Responsible for corporate sales with business partners (banks, insurances, car forums, affiliated companies...)
- 19. And other projects & assignment from BOD



Handled Mai Linh taxi for fleet sales of thousands Nissan cars from 2011 to 2017



Closed fleet sales of 200 units Navara to Viettel corp; 302 units to Ministry of Defense; 200 units to social bank; and other fleet to Ministry of public security; MOH; MOF...



From June 2017 to now SONGHONG international human resource and trading company.

Market development Manager

- Working with Japanese cooperatives for human resource cooperation contract.
- Recruit Vietnamese young labour and student.
- Conduct Japanese training before entering Japan.
- Support Vietnamese labour and student in Japan for life and work...





MY EXPECTATION POSITION

- Salary: more than JPY300,000 per month (depended on job)
- Working hour: negotiable
- Working place: the first priority is Tokyo/Nagoya/Osaka or other provinces at KANTO, KANSAI, CHUBU
- Job: Vietnam related trading, business, management...
 - Collaborate with Japanese companies to invest in Vietnam
 - > Support Vietnamese investors for business in Japan
 - > Transfer of technology and equipment from Japan
 - Purchase special vehicles (ambulances, cash carrying vehicles ...) and automobiles spare parts from Japan
 - Consulting for labor export, Vietnamese students to Japan
 - ightharpoonup Programs on culture, education, health \cdots between Japan $\ \&$ Vietnam

Other expectation: company support for living house and transportation.

EDUCATION & LANGUAGES

1998 – 2002: Bachelor of Japanese – Hanoi foreign languages university

2005 – 2008: Economic - foreign Relations – Foreign Trade University

Other important training courses & certificates:

No	Year	Month	Training courses - Certificates - Qualifications	
1	2002	7	Bachelor of Japanese – Hanoi foreign languages university	
2	2009	2	Certificated by Nissan Motor Japan – Area Manager Training	
3	2009	10	Certificate by Nissan Middle East for Customer Handling Training - The standard course for Trainer	
4	2011	10	Certificate by Nissan Middle East for Advanced Customer Handling Training - The course for Trainer	
5	2009	8	Certificate for effective presentation skill	
6	2010	11	Certificate for first step to management - supervisory skill	
7	2010	7	Certificate for Key account management	
8	2005	5	Total Quality Management (TQM) by Honda Motor Japan	
9	2005	5	Honda marketing and Management seminar (HMMS) by Honda Motor Japan	
10	2006	3	Product/hospitality/complaint handling courses by Honda Motor Japan	
11	2009	8	N-CAM (NSC Competitive Advantage Map) the guideline for set up automobile business of Nissan worldwide	
12	2009	9	S-DOM (Sales – Dealer Operation Mandatory) by Nissan Motor Japan	

Languages:

- Vietnamese mother tongue
- Japanese N2 level
- English Good enough for working with foreigner

Computer skill: professional & good for working

References:

- 1. Mr. Ho Hai An Honda Vietnam's Director +84211-3868-888
- 2. Mr. Teh Kim Hwa Nissan Vietnam's Director +8424-7301-1333

Thank you very much and best regards.

Pham Trung Tinh